

### **BRAND STATEMENT:**

As a Full Stack Developer, my mission is to add value to your company. I am an excited and enthusiastic person, who's inquisitive about life. Whether it's for my job, or taking the initiative to learn on my own, I have always been hard-working. For me, passion is a key attribute that determines the outcome of your success. Last year I won the 2015 Quarter One Best Non-sell Associate, for my outstanding contributions to my teams, and I realize that when we work together, we achieve the best results. Having led an unorthodox career path, my personal experiences and straightforward approach make me unique and adaptable to any situation. I want to impact the world through my imaginative approach to make life more enjoyable for people.

### **EXPERIENCE:**

#### **General Assembly**

10/2016 - 1/2017

# The White Transvaal Lion: Shooting Game

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, jQuery

- Designed a game that renders in the browser
- Implemented logic for winning and displayed win or lose states

#### **London Playhouse**

HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Express, Mustache, Fetch, Bcrypt, Body-Parser, Curl

- · Application pulling information from an API
- Full Stack CRUD application with log in capabilities

#### GA Lunch Break

HTML/CSS, Ruby on Rails, Google Maps API, Javascript, Postgresql, Materialize, BCrypt, Sessions, Gon Gem

- Group oriented web application that recommends local area dining
- Implemented logic for winning and displayed win or lose states

## Lord & Taylor: Fulfillment Associate 9/2013 - 10/2016

- · Accurately picked e-commerce orders by style, color, and size
- Shipped orders to various customers using FedEx
- Promoted from stock to fulfillment associate
- Received the 1st Quarter Best Non-Sales Award for 2015

## The Gap: Sales Associate

5/2011 - 12/2012

- Organized the sales floor according to the company standards
- Prioritized between management tasks and assisting customers
- Analyzed and solved customer problems when debating purchases

# **Everett Publishing: Executive Assistant**

1/2011 - 5/2011

- Provided executive level administrative support to the Founder
- Supplied sponsors for the Alex: The Magazine Relaunch Party
- Arranged meetings, appointments and recorded minutes
- Researched competitors and provided ideas for rebranding

# TECHNICAL SKILLS:

HTML5, CSS3, Ruby, SQL, Node.js, React.js, Express.js, Mustache.js, ¡Query, Bootstrap, Ruby on Rails, Sinatra, RSpec, PostgreSQL, AJAX, ISON

#### Other:

Adobe Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop

## **EDUCATION:**

## **General Assembly:**

Web Development Immersive

## The New School:

Graphic Design

## Montclair State Univeristy:

**Fashion Studies** 

## **VOLUNTEER:**

#### Volunteers of America:

**Operation Backpack** Toys for the Holiday